Keshia-Lee washington, DC 914.374.3737 **Martin**

Email: keshialeemartin@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/keshia-lee-martin-05388a75/

GitHub: https://github.com/eeleelksm

A Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp Student at the George Washington University Coding Program. Experience with being a multitasking Team Lead remotely. An enthusiastic gamer with an interest in Game Programming and Game Design with aptitude for innovation and creativity.

Skills

Operating Systems: PC, Mac, iOS, PlayStation, XBOX, Nintendo Switch

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frameworks:, Express.js, Node.js, Bootstrap

Databases: MySQL Tools: Git. GitHub. Heroku

CRM: Salesforce, ConnectWise, HubSpot

Bug Reporting: Buganizer, JIRA

Other Skills: Quality Control, Quality Assurance

Projects

December 2021: Play tester for MOBA game – AOV: Arena of Valor

Experience

TapSEC Consulting, LLC / Part-Time Marketing Assistant

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT, WASHINGTON, D.C.

- Providing administrative support associated with information technology and telecommunications
- Tracking leads, opportunities, and updating information in various CRM
- Preparing reports, presentations, NDAs and teaming agreements
- Sending and organizing emails and calendar invites of multiple email accounts

US Tech Solutions / Lead Quality Assurance Operations Analyst

JANUARY 2020 - JULY 2021, WASHINGTON, D.C. Google Contract

- Oversaw and guided a team of 13 agents and contractors in the QA of early voting, drop box, and Election Day polling locations, gubernatorial and down ballot candidates, and election department contact information from all US counties for Google's Where to Vote Search tool for the US 2020 General Election
- Triaged real time feedback using Buganizer and forwarding to company partners to improve the Where to Vote Search tool
- Kept track of Civic Information API errors reported by users and developers and overseeing the Civic Information API Forum
- Created and edited data quality procedure and user feedback documents for current and future use

Crowdstaffing / Quality Assurance Data Analyst

AUGUST 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018, WASHINGTON, D.C. Google Contract

- Ensured the accuracy and quality of data using Google's Where to Vote tool used for the US 2018 Midterm Elections
- Individual research of all polling locations, gubernatorial and down ballot candidates, and election department's contact information from counties of all 50 states and the District of Columbia
- Triaged real time feedback and information using Buganizer to identify errors and improve the applications

Elite Personnel / Quality Control Assistant

MAY 2017 - AUGUST 2018, WASHINGTON, D.C. American Institutes of Research Contract

- Conducted QA checks for online reports in Test, UAT, and Production of standardized tests across state clients using Microsoft Excel and JIRA
- · Created mockups and UAT documents for state clients using Microsoft Word
- Used detailed specification documents to QC accurate reports based on the state client's requirements and guidelines

SAX Dinner Theatre and Lounge / Professional Performer and Co-Captain DECEMBER 2014 - JULY 2019, WASHINGTON, D.C.

National Cancer Institute / Unofficial Research Intern

AUGUST 2014 - MAY 2017, ROCKVILLE, MD

Publications

Analysis of Covariance: Nonparametric *StatsRef: Statistics Reference Online* NOVEMBER 2017 – EDITED FROM ORIGINAL BY VANCE BERGER

Per Family Error Rates: A Response *Modern Applied Statistical Methods* MAY 2015 – WRITTEN WITH JAMES F. TROENDLE AND VANCE BERGER

Adaptive Random Assignment *StatsRef: Statistics Reference Online* MARCH 2015 – EDITED FROM ORIGINAL BY YANYAN ZHOU VANCE BERGER

Education

The George Washington University / GW Coding Boot Camp

AUGUST 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022, REMOTE - CERTIFICATE PENDING

Yellowbrick / FIT Gaming and Esports Industry Essential CertificateISSUED DECEMBER 2021 – NO EXPIRATION DATE

The American University / Bachelor of Science

AUGUST 2007 - AUGUST 2014, WASHINGTON, DC

MAJOR: Statistics, MINOR: Business Administration